Guide to the Noël Riley Fitch Julia Child Papers MSS.323
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Appetite for Life: The Biography of Julia Child
  - Subseries C: Drafts and Proofs
    - Appetite for Life [Copyedited Manuscript before Doubleday, 2 of 3], 1996 - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Appetite for Life [Copyedited Manuscript before Doubleday, 3 of 3], 1996 - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Appetite for Life [Proof, 1 of 2], 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Appetite for Life [Proof, 2 of 2], 1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - "Chapter 1: Beginnings" (1945, 1949 - 1912), December 1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - "Chapter 2: A Place in the Sun" (1849 - 1927), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - "Chapter 3: Education of an Extrovert", 1996 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - "Chapter 4: Smith College: Ivy Walls and Jelly Donuts" (Drafts, 1930 - 1934), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "Chapter 5: Career Search" (Drafts, 1934 - 1942), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - "Chapter 6: India Intrigue" (Drafts, 1944 - 1945), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - "Chapter 7: To China With Love" (Drafts, 1945), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Chapter 8: Eastward Ho" (Choosing a New Home Drafts, December 1945 - 1946), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - "Chapter 9: Flavours of Marriage" (Early Marriage Drafts, 1946 - 1948), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - "Chapter 10: À Paris" (Drafts, November 1948 - 1949), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - "Chapter 11: Coron Bleu" (Drafts, 1949 - 1952), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Chapter 12: Marseille" (Drafts, 1953 - 1954), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Chapter 13: A Little Town in Germany" (Bonn Drafts, October 1954 - October 1956), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "Chapter 14: Back Home (and Cooking) on the Range" (DC November 1956 - March 1959), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Chapter 15: 'I am at heart a Viking.' " (Norway, May 1959 - May 1961), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "Chapter 16: Launching the Book" (Launching a Career, June 1961 - 1962), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - "Chapter 17: The French Chef" (1963 - 1964), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Chapter 18: Winters in Provence" (1965 - 1967), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "Chapter 19: The Media are the Message" (National Coverage, 1967 - 1968), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Chapter 20: Celebrity and Solitude" (1968 - 1970), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "Chapter 21: Persian Circles: In Color, In Person" (1970 - 1974), 1996 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - "Chapter 22: Transitions" (1974 - 1977), 1996 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "Chapter 23: The Company She Keeps" (1977 - 1980), 1996 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - "Chapter 24: Pacific Overture" (1981 - 1984), 1996 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - "Chapter 25: Seasoned With Love" (1985 - 1989), 1996 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - "Chapter 26: La Notre Dame de la Cuisine" (1989 - 1993), 1996 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - "Chapter 27: Do Not Go Gentle" (1994 - 1997), 1996 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Appetite for Life: Proofs, "Loose Correx", August 1, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Appetite for Life: Confirmation / Repro Proofs [1 of 3], July 10 [no year] (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Appetite for Life: Confirmation / Repro Proofs [2 of 3], July 10 [no year] (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Appetite for Life: Confirmation / Repro Proofs [3 of 3], July 10 [no year] (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Editors Proofs [1 of 5], April 25, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Editors Proofs [2 of 5], April 25, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Editors Proofs [3 of 5], April 25, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Editors Proofs [4 of 5], April 25, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Editors Proofs [5 of 5], April 25, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Editors Proofs: "Western Pioneers and Blue Blood", undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Appetite for Life: Editors Proofs Part 2 [1 of 4], July 10, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Appetite for Life: Editors Proofs Part 2 [2 of 4], July 10, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Appetite for Life: Editors Proofs Part 2 [3 of 4], July 10, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Appetite for Life: Editors Proofs Part 2 [4 of 4], July 10, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Final Draft [Marked by Albert Sonnenfeld, Noel Riley Fitch, 1 of 4], December 1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Final Draft [Marked by Albert Sonnenfeld, Noel Riley Fitch, 2 of 4], December 1996 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Final Draft [Marked by Albert Sonnenfeld, Noel Riley Fitch, 3 of 4], December 1996 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Final Draft [Marked by Albert Sonnenfeld, Noel Riley Fitch, 4 of 4], December 1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - "The Innards" [Galley Proofs of Zeros and Ones by Sadie Plant, 1 of 5], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - "The Innards" [Galley Proofs of Zeros and Ones by Sadie Plant, 2 of 5], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - "The Innards" [Galley Proofs of Zeros and Ones by Sadie Plant, 3 of 5], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "The Innards" [Galley Proofs of Zeros and Ones by Sadie Plant, 4 of 5], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "The Innards" [Galley Proofs of Zeros and Ones by Sadie Plant, 5 of 5], 1997 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Notes / Materials Re: Proofreading, Corrections, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Subseries D: Publication, Publicity and Reception
    Subseries D: Publication, Publicity and Reception generally follows original order, but is arranged chronologically when material is dated. It consists of material related to the publication of Appetite for Life including book proposals and correspondence with publishers, as well as post-publication materials including correspondence and ephemera related to publicity of the book, reviews and correspondence related to reception, correspondence and documents related to film rights, and correspondence and research materials related to articles and writing by Noël Riley Fitch on Julia Child following publication of the biography.
    - Answered Correspondence, 1993 - 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Book Proposal, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Child Proposal - Earliest Drafts, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Catalog, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Flyer: Bathtub, October 1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Queries, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Doubleday Catalog, 1997 - 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Pre-Publication Mentions of Appetite for Life, 1997 - 1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Reviews of Appetite for Life, 1996 - 2010 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Responses to Appetite for Life, 2009 - 2012 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Articles Mentioning Julia Child, 2009 - 2010 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Response Letters for Appetite for Life [1 of 2], 2002 - 2010 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Response Letters for Appetite for Life [2 of 2], 1997 - 2007 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Handwriting Analysis of Paul Child, 2011 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Dust Jacket Covers, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - "Julie and Julia" Film Infringement, 2008 - 2010, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Julia Child Film Rights, 1997 - 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Los Angeles Magazine Excerpt From Appetite for Life, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - "Julia Child: The OSS Years," The Wall Street Journal, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - "Julia: The Book" - American Institute of Wine and Food Newsletter, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - "A New Beginning for Julia Child" - AIWF, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - "Sally's Place Essay", 1999 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Curnonsky - Child Article in Gastronomica, 2004 - 2005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Child in Paris - Paris Notes, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Doubleday Promotion / Publicity: Appetite for Life, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - No Answer, 1992 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Julia Child Personality, 1994 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Legal Questions, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Blurbs for Appetite for Life, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - French Culinary Institute - Hamilton Launch, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Pre-Publication Publicity, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Advertisements, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - OSS Book by Jennet Conant, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Noël Riley Fitch Articles and Lectures on Julia Child, 1998 - 2012 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Julia Articles - Future, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Edible Los Angeles: Article, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Doubleday TV Publicity: ABC News, A & E, 1997 - 2000, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Nin - Miller - Child Connection, 1946, 1966 - 1967, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Appetite for Life: Promotion Tour, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Julia Child and California Food Essay, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Flyers / Postcards, 1996 - 1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Reviews of Appetite for Life, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, Events, 2013-2014 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Books & Cooks Event, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Boston, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Santa Barbara, 1994-2002 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Appearances Schedules, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Fort Lauderdale, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Idaho, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Providence Pubic Library -- Event, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Research and Promotion for Julia Bio, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - June Appearance Julia Child, 2018 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Joan Cusack Movie Option, 2005-2012 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
    - E-Books Julia Child, 2008-2018 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Be Our Guest Gifted and Signed By Author, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Washington, DC (Past), 1993-2004 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Julia Child Papers, 2011-2013 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Napa Valley, 1985-2016 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Photographs and Images
    Subseries E: Photos and Images has been retained in original order. It consists of photos of and related to Julia Child used as source material for Appetite for Life including those printed in the book, other images such as comics related to Julia Child, and photographs related to the publicity of Appetite for Life.
    - Mc Williams Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Weston Family, circa 1900 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Caro and John Mc Williams - Tennis, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Baby Julia in Chair, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Julia - Childhood, 1912 - 1922 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Parents - Babies 1911+, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 3 Mc Williams Toddlers, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Grade School Children with Mother, 1923 - 1924 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Childhood, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Child Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Relatives, 1923 - 1930 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Julia - Arm Out, La Jolla, 1926, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - 9th Grade Graduating Class of Polytechnic School - Pasadena, CA, 1927, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Smith College, 1935, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Gang of Five, Smith College Junior Prom, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Amherst Prom, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Julia and Car, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Mother Caro, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - 1207 South Pasadena Avenue, undated, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Julia and John at Beach, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Julia Child - St. Malo, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Pop and Phila, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Julia on Steps, St. Malo, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - "Ham" Junior League Play - Pasadena, CA, 1934 - 1944 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Julia, John, and Dorothy, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Julia Child - Ceylon, 1944, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Paul Child - New Delhi, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Paul Child - India, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Julia on Cot - Kandy, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Julia Child - China, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - China, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Paul Child - Paris Apartment, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Julia + Paul - McHumpsh and Mowrers, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Paris, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Julia in Window - Paris, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Julia and Paul Wedding, September 1, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Child, Charley / Freddy, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Paul and Charlie - Rock Pulling, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Julia on Grass, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Paul and Helene, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Julia at Stove, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Dort and Julia - Paris, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Julia - 1950s (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Grown Mc Williams Family - Dort's Wedding, June 23, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Paul and Julia in Living Room with Cat, January 1950 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Bertholle, Beck, and Child: Ecole des 3 Gourmandes, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Hemingway Wedding, June 25, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Julia Child and Simone Beck - Chinon, April 6, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Marseilles, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Jerry Hill's Place in Cassis, July 20, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Bonn - Valentine's Day Card, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - A.I.W.F. - Florida, undated (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - A.I.W.F., October 5, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Paul's Paintings, undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Appetite for Life: Prints, various (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Photo Business, 1994 - 1997 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Julia Child, Memoranda Book, [Paul Child], undated (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Julia Child Cartoons, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - "Photos Misc.", 1997 - 1999 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Cordon Bleu, undated (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Julia and Paul - Paris Party, undated (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Julia, Nancy Davis, Kids, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Julia Child - 1960s (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Correcting Index - Maine, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Julia Child and James Beard - Beard House, May 21, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Bramafan - Julia at Table, undated (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Simone Beck, undated (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - La Pitchoune, undated (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Founders A.I.W.F., undated (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Julia Child and Ruth Lockwood, "Dinner in 1/2 an Hour", November 4, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Julia with Ecole des 3 Gourmandes Patch, January 17, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - M.F.K. Fisher, 1960s (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Julia Child - 1970s (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Julia and Paul by Ted Palenbaum, undated (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Saltonstall, Child, Fiedler - Golden Door Award, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Julia Child - 1980s (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Letter about Photo of Julia Child + Noel Riley Fitch, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - "Pix at Child House" [Xerox Only], undated (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Master Chefs - Michlin, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Julia Child - 1990s (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - Poly Tech Pasadena Classmates, Chicago AIWF Event, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - Julia Child Slides, undated (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - Appetite for Life: Slides, Paris Restaurants, Rubber Stamps, undated (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - Book Photos [Xeroxes], 1997 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - Fitch and Julia Child, 1992, 1996, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Series II: The Grand Literary Cafés of Europe
  This series consists of correspondence, ephemera and documents related to the research, publication and publicity of The Grand Literary Cafés of Europe. Original order has been retained.
  - Grand Literary Cafés of Europe: Articles and Emails, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Grand Literary Cafés of Europe: UCLA Event Photographs, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Editor - Kate Mitchell, Julie Delf [Correspondence], 2005 - 2006 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Cafes - Correspondence, 1988, 2006, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - U.S. Coffee Houses, 2005 - 2007 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Coffee, circa 2006, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence about Photos, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - W. Scott Haines, 2004 - 2005, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cafés General, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Side Bars, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The Grand Literary Cafés of Europe: Bibliography, 2004 - 2005 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Coffee Chains, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Other Cities - Other Cafés, various (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Time Line, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Grand Literary Cafés of Europe: Color Illustrations, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Introduction, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Drafts [1 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Drafts [2 of 2], undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - List of Cafés, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Edited Text, June 29, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - First Page Proofs, August 8, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Second Page Proofs, September 2005 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Page Proofs, October, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Reviews - European Cafés, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Amsterdam, The Netherlands - Dutch, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Barcelona, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Berlin, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Bucharest, Romania, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Budapest, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Copenhagen, Denmark, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Dublin, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Madrid, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Milan, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Moscow, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Munich, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Norway - Oslo, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Padova, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Le Grand Véfour, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - La Closerie des Lilas, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Saint-Germain-des-Prés, 2004 - 2005 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Paris, 1999 - 2005 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Acknowledgements, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Wolf Koerner, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Florence, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Leipzig, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lisbon, Portugal, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - London Intro, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Café Royal, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Kettners, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - St. Petersberg, 1999 - 2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Prague, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Rome, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Salzburg, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Vienna, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Café Griensteidl, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Café Central, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Café Landtmann, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Café Sperl (Vienna), 2005 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Venice, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Zurich, Switzerland, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Stockholm, Sweden, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Palermo, Sicily, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Café Zeyer, 1992 - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Literary Cafés / Food Literature / Others, 1988 - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Hotel Flyers, various (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Pix - for Line Drawings, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Cafés - Intro, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Brasserie Lipp, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Deux Magots, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Café de Flore, circa 1991 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Le Montana, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - La Palette, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Le Petit Saint-Benoit, circa 1988 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Pont Royal Bar, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Restaurant des Beaux Arts, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Montparnasse Cafés, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - La Coupole, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Poland and Krakow Poland, 2000-2015 (Box 28, Folder 12-13)
  - Chicago, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Pre-Pub Articles, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Cafes Collection Research, 2013-2014 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2015 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Appearances, Publicity, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Series III: Literary Cafés of Paris
  This series consists of correspondence, ephemera and documents related to the research, publication and publicity of the Literary Cafés of Paris. Original order has been retained.
  - Dingo Bar, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Le Dôme, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Falstaff, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Café Francois Coppee, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Jockey, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Rotonde, undated (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Latin Quarter Cafés, undated (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Brasserie Balzar, 1984, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Café de la Mairie, undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Polidor, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Procope, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Lapérouse, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Le Boeuf sur le Toit, 2003 - 2004 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Ma Bourgogne, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Le Fouquet's, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Café de la Paix, undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Pranier, 1992 - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Bars - Paris Literary / Alcohol, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Hemingway Bar / Ritz, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Harry's New York Bar, 1988 - 1989 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Lapin Agile, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Photograph Orders, 1988 - 1990 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Starhill Press, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Elliot & Clark Cafés - 2nd Publishing, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Black Belt - River City Press, 3rd Publishing Cafés, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Series IV: Paris Café: The Select Crowd
  This series consists of correspondence, ephemera and documents related to the research, publication and publicity of Paris Café: The Select Crowd. Original order has been retained.
  - Paris Café: The Select Crowd: Proof, 2005 - 2006 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Tulka, Rick [Post Publishing], 2007 - 2008 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Soft Scull / Richard, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Tulka Letters, 2003 - 2010 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - MS Prep and Additives / Tulka, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Research - Cafés, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Interviews, 2004 - 2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Publisher Select, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Expenses, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Additional Illustrations - Colored, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Mock - Up, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - English Version, August 2006 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 1) Proofs, August 2007 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 2) Proofs, July 27, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - French Translation, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Korean Translation, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "MS Prep Instru", 2007 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Marketing, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Quotes, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Cover, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Title Page Outline, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Introduction, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - History, March 8, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Day in Life Seasons, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Clientel, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Food, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Food - Revised, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Croque - Monsieur, February 19, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - French Onion Soup, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Welsh Rarebit, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Drunks, March 9, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Resume, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Select: Reviews and Catalog, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Publicity, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Paris Notes - Montparnasse Select, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - "Selecting the Select" / Essay - Article, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Rendez-vous au Sélect: Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Paris Café: The Select Crowd: Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Paris Café: The Select Crowd: First Version, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Paris Café: The Select Crowd: [Proof with Colored Illustrations], undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Paris Café: The Select Crowd: Proof, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Paris Café: The Select Crowd: Proofs 2 / 3, August 3, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Rick Tulka: "Le Select" Les Clients, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Illustrations, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Series V: Noël Riley Fitch Personal Materials
  This series contains information on the professional and personal life of Noël Riley Fitch, including cooking-related memorabilia, professional biographies and resumes, and a collection of menus from restaurants across the United States and Europe. Original order has been retained.
  - Pet Milk Cookbook, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NRF Books, Finding Aid, Professional Life, 1997, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Albert Sonnenfeld, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Future Project Ideas, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)